This incidentally, is why
Hollywood is making lots and lots of sequels
Because there's two things by a chap called William Goldman who wrote books about movies. He also wrote the screenplay to two very famous movies, The Princess Bride and
Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid. And he said
The important thing to know about movies is that nobody knows anything, so nobody knows which movies are going to be a hit
The other thing to know about movies is nothing is as cheap as a hit. So if you make a movie and it's a hit
The money that you make from it is just
Amazing compared to the amount of money that it cost.
But those two things together result in movie companies ending up essentially trying to make the same movie over and over again
Preferably with the same title and a number added on the end of it, because that is a much safer bet than actually just trying to do something completely new.
And so by upping the bet, you're doing something like that
Not quite the same, but you're doing something which is a sequel to what you've done up to that point. And so it's a much more informed bet.